var questions = [{
	
	"question":"The first mechannical computer designed by Charles Babbage was called ?",
	"option1":"Abacus",
	"option2":"Analytical Engine",
	"option3":"Calculator",
	"option4":"Processor",
	"answer":"2"
	
},{
	
	"question":"Which of the following is the most powerful type of computer ?",
	"option1":"Super - micro",
	"option2":"Super conductor",
	"option3":"Super computer",
	"option4":"Megaframe",
	"answer":"3"
	
},{
	
	"question":"Which is a signle integrated circuit ?",
	"option1":"Gate",
	"option2":"Mother Board",
	"option3":"Chip",
	"option4":"CPU",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	
	"question":"C is ?",
	"option1":"A third generation high level language",
	"option2":"A machine language",
	"option3":"An assembly language",
	"option4":"All of the above",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	
	"question":"Web pages are writtten using ?",
	"option1":"FTP",
	"option2":"HTTP",
	"option3":"HTML",
	"option4":"URL",
	"answer":"3"
},{
	
	"question":"UNIVAC is an example of",
	"option1":"First generation computer",
	"option2":"Second generation computer",
	"option3":"Third generation computer",
	"option4":"Fourth generation computer",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	
	"question":"Which of the following is an example of non volatile memory ?",
	"option1":"VLSI",
	"option2":"LSI",
	"option3":"ROM",
	"option4":"RAM",
	"answer":"3"
},{
	
	"question":"Graphic interfaces were first used in a xerox product is called ?",
	"option1":"Ethernet",
	"option2":"Inter LISP",
	"option3":"Small talk",
	"option4":"Zeta LISP",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	"question":"Find the odd one out?",
	"option1":"ORACLE",
	"option2":"SYBASE",
	"option3":"C",
	"option4":"INFORMIX",
	"answer":"3"
	
},{
	"question":"The ------ is the administrative section of the computer system?",
	"option1":"Memory Unit",
	"option2":"Input Unit",
	"option3":"Central Processing Unit",
	"option4":"Control Unit",
	"answer":"3"
}



];